I am so excited to be here. I even got
some work done for the first time.
Exciting, right? I got lip fillers,
right? Yeah. Not not in these lips.
Jesus. [laughter]
Could you imagine? No. It's a full
Kardashian situation down here, right?
Men say they want a woman with a fat ass
and a wet [\h__\h] Well, sorry fellas. I
got a fat [\h__\h] and a wet ass.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> That's a disgusting way to start the
show. [laughter]
No, the the lip fillers are not going to
age well. I keep gaining weight. I I
gained about 40 lbs this last year and I
know I gained weight cuz I was walking
down the street and this old guy cat
called me. He was like, "Damn, baby. I
bet you got a great personality.
[laughter]
Objectify
me, you piece of [\h__\h] Come on. No, I
look good for a new mom, though, right?
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Um, I'm not uh [laughter]
just look good for
No, I was hoping that the weight gain
would go to all the good spots, you
know, go to my boobs, go to my ass. That
didn't happen. Okay. Went straight to my
chins and my nipples.
[laughter]
That's not what you want. We got big
nips in Carl's bad. What are we working
with?
[\h__\h] liars. I see some heavy naturals
in the back. Come on. [laughter]
Got an Areola Borealis out tonight.
No, I do have big nipples. They're
medically significant. Uh [laughter]
we're in the 90th percentile
[laughter]
according to my dentist. Uh,
he's a good guy. [laughter]
Very thorough. Uh,
no. I don't like going to the doctor now
that I've gained weight. My doctor's
super judgmental. She body shames me
with facts about myself. It's rude, you
know. [laughter]
She was looking at my charts. She was
like, "Oh, wow. Your BMI is 34.
You're obese."
I was like, "You're a [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> She said, "Does obesity run in your
family?" [\h__\h] nothing runs in
[laughter] my family.
HOW YOU THINK we got here?
[laughter]
She said, "Good news is you can drop an
easy 30 lbs if you just quit drinking.
Bad news is [laughter]
I don't drink."
[laughter]
Little presumptuous. [laughter]
No. I went to my doctor to get a
papsmear. Anybody else in the BDSM? No.
Okay. [laughter]
I hate getting pap smears. They're
uncomfortable. They're painful. I hate
waiting for the results. I always get
really stressed out. And I actually got
my results back today. And it turns out
I have the tightest [\h__\h] she's ever
seen. So, [cheering]
no. No, no, no, no, no. It's HPV. Um,
[laughter]
you should wash your hands.
I'm so happy to be here, you guys. I
love doing standup. I do. I used to do
improv comedy. Do you guys know what
improv is? Yeah, of course. All right.
There is weird tension, though, between
improv comedians and stand-up comedians,
which is stupid, you know, cuz we're all
just trying to make people laugh, right?
Like the only difference is that
stand-up comedians want to kill
themselves. [laughter]
And improv comedians make you want to
kill yourself. [laughter]
That's it, right? My ex used to do
improv. I'm no longer with him. I'm
single now. I'm single by choice. Thank
you. [cheering]
Yeah. Thank you. It was his choice. Uh
[laughter]
he was a shitty guy, you know. We were
hanging out at his place, which was a 93
Corolla. And uh [laughter]
he told me I had the face of a fat third
grade teacher
and the body of a fat third grader.
Not a nice guy. Didn't like that he was
looking at kids. [laughter]
Jokes on him though, cuz he was
infertile. He was sterile. Sterile
Daryl, right? Shooting blanks. And call
me crazy, but I like my jizz with some
pulp in it. Okay. [laughter] If there's
no risk, there's no reward,
[\h__\h]
All right. You guys like the pulp. You
guys are cool. [laughter] What the [\h__\h]
are you guys drinking? Just zero. Live a
little. The [\h__\h] It's hardly any
calories, right? [laughter]
It is. It is only five calories.
And I know this cuz in my calorie
tracking app, [laughter]
it says human semen. Five calories.
>> Why do they specify humans? [laughter]
Also, who are these healthconscious [\h__\h]
guzzlers
[laughter]
documenting every load? What? I don't
include all of my cheat meals.
[laughter]
[\h__\h] crazy.
No, my my ex was a shitty guy. He was.
But I I miss him. I do. It's stupid.
said I miss him. Okay. And so recently I
started fingering myself worse
[laughter]
to remember him.
Only the women are laughing. [laughter]
Like I'll just flick my urethra for
hours. Right. [laughter]
This guy's like, "WHAT'S THE URETHRA?"
[laughter]
You'll find it.
No. Make some noise if you're a guy and
you can confidently find the [\h__\h] Let's
hear it, man. LET'S HEAR IT. ALPHAS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. Prove it. [laughter]
Come up [screaming] here
underneath my Snoopy sweatpants.
[laughter]
SHOW ME MY [\h__\h] clip
cuz I can't find it. [laughter]
Sorry, that probably smelled. Uh,
I'm a teacher. Uh, [laughter]
thank you. Yeah, thank you. [laughter]
Thank you.
No, I'm I'm a middle school English
teacher. I I love Yeah. Thank you. All
right. [laughter]
One, two, three. Eyes on me.
No, I I love my job. I do. I hate my
students. Uh, [laughter]
worst people I know, truly. Right.
No, we're at the end of the year now and
I had a kid come into my class, super
quiet kid, little weirdo, and he waited
for all the other kids to leave and he
looked at me and he was like, "Hey, Miss
H, can I come on your face?
Come on, dude." Right? So, I sat him
down. I looked him dead in his face and
I was like, "Daniel, you cannot speak to
your teacher this way. Okay. It's super
inappropriate, right? It's may I come on
your face. [laughter]
We've been over this.
Jesus. No. Did you guys know that if you
eat enough of something, your [\h__\h] starts
to taste like it? Have you heard that?
Oh, he knows. [laughter]
Little mischievous giggle.
So, like if you eat a lot of garlic,
your [\h__\h] is really bitter, right? You
eat a lot of pineapple, your [\h__\h] is
really sweet. Right? Like your come pray
tastes like protein powder, right?
[laughter]
She's like can confirm very chalky.
She's stealing all your gains, bro.
Waking up every morning like more
[screaming]
calm.
[laughter]
No, I was thinking about this though and
I was like, "Holy [\h__\h] is that why my
ex-boyfriend's come always tasted like
his roommates?
But do you get it? [laughter]
>> It's uh it's hard to be a woman comic
sometimes. It's hard to be a young woman
comic. I'm 27. I've done this since I
was 19. Thank you. Yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
And it's not always glamorous like it is
tonight, right? You know, sometimes I
get followed to my car after shows or
harassed by comedians or audience
members. It's not great. And I want to
be honest on stage and I want to be
personal, but I'm always navigating what
I say and what I don't say because I
don't want to get [\h__\h] with. And I
used to tell this joke about having a
double-jointed jaw, which is true, but
pretty innocuous. And I don't tell that
joke anymore because the last time I
told it, this old skin tag of a man came
up to me.
He didn't have any teeth. He put his arm
around me, started massaging my neck,
and he said, "You got a doublejinted
jaw,
and you're up here telling jokes instead
of sucking dicks.
You're a waste of a woman.
You're not living up to your [\h__\h]
potential."
And I said, "Excuse me, sir. You don't
have any teeth.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU'RE NOT LIVING UP TO YOUR [\h__\h]
POTENTIAL. Thank you guys so much.
[cheering]
>> [music]